This falls, stars fade away
Oh, she got hit her Tokyo shadows calling
Yami no michi ga haji maru
Chasing dreams through endless night
You may want one at night
But I'm tears become our pain
Time moves fire, my dreams are still
Cocoa wise shini maru, oh voices
And go across the void
Moody, every good
Drawing through the shadows
Escaping every light
Mirage has shittered
Promises broken, burning through the night
Oh shini negairo
Let's break out from the prison of night
Say you come, in the darkness we rise
Fading with love
Yami no nagada
You've been following me, never given
I can't even know you there
Together we face our darkest fear
Yami no me, now you're me too close
Sun's ray jump, all we forge is your head
Maybe this is a familiar
I ever was covered in a heart
Something I don't know what
Time moves fire, our hearts turn to stone
Cocoa wise shini maru, oh voices
And go across the void
Moody, every good
Drawing through the shadows
Escaping every light
Mirage has shittered
Promises broken, burning through the night
Oh shini negairo
Let's break out from the prison of night
Say you come, in the darkness we rise
Fading with love
Beyond the fire, never burning
Brought a noble cry, our power destroys the world tonight
I won't go back, even in darkness
My friends remain!
Spookishu no hikari
Break your wings and fly through the plain
Cocoa no masu, oh voices
Drawing through the shadows
Escaping every light
Mirage has shittered
Promises broken, burning through the night
Oh shini negairo
Let's break out from the prison of night
Say you come, in the darkness we rise
Fading with love
Beyond the shadows
Escaping every light
Mirage has shittered
Promises broken, burning through the night
Oh shini negairo
Let's break out from the prison of night
Say you come, in the darkness we rise
Fading with love
Beyond the shadows
In the darkness we rise
Fading with love